<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:iweb="http://www.apple.com/iweb" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Hazzard’s Hypotheses</title>
    <link>http://brianhazzard.com/Brian_Hazzards_Blog/Blog/Blog.html</link>
    <description>I am a software professional and independent musician. I jump head first into new interests, without apology. Right now I’m interested in modern web technologies, designer board games, and Virginia wines.&lt;br/&gt;I live in the small town of Blacksburg, VA with my beautiful wife Crystal, and my evil cat Spencer. This is my story.</description>
    <generator>iWeb 3.0.4</generator>
    <image>
      <url>http://brianhazzard.com/Brian_Hazzards_Blog/Blog/Blog_files/183665_10100125708535943_6205556_51812403_2462582_n.jpg</url>
      <title>Hazzard’s Hypotheses</title>
      <link>http://brianhazzard.com/Brian_Hazzards_Blog/Blog/Blog.html</link>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>The Post that Started it All</title>
      <link>http://brianhazzard.com/Brian_Hazzards_Blog/Blog/Entries/2012/2/11_The_Post_that_Started_it_All.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">33ce4182-ec72-4de2-b762-55dd1a1d0edb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2012 16:52:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://brianhazzard.com/Brian_Hazzards_Blog/Blog/Entries/2012/2/11_The_Post_that_Started_it_All_files/SAM_1670.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://brianhazzard.com/Brian_Hazzards_Blog/Blog/Media/object009_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:255px; height:136px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;“Who the hell are you?”&lt;br/&gt;First of all, the title of this post isn’t quite right. It implies that I created something important, relevant, and meaningful, and that this post is responsible for that something’s existence. Well, I’ve created a lot of things, and I’d like to think that some of those things are important, relevant or meaningful. But certainly, nothing I’ve done has been all three.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Rather the title was quite arbitrary, but it’s contents will not be. My intention is to introduce myself, and so that’s what I shall do: My name is Brian Hazzard (just Hazzard to most people). I’m a software professional, an independent musician, and a board gamer. And that’s what this blog will be all about: my life, my career in technology, my music, and my enjoyment of board games.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;“Why write another boring blog?”&lt;br/&gt;Well, I hope it won’t be boring. Honestly, I’m a pretty opinionated guy, and lots of my opinions don’t jive with common thinking. For example, here are a few of my opinions that future posts will touch on:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;	-	Almost everyone who thinks they know what a REST API is all about, is dead wrong. I’ll offer insights (that I’ve synthesized from people smarter than me) about what I think is wrong with your API, what you can do differently, and why it will change your life.&lt;br/&gt;	-	Board games are WAY cooler than video games. They facilitate deep and meaningful social interactions, stimulate strategic and tactical thought, and have more replay value than any video game.&lt;br/&gt;	-	The world is heading towards open information. Copyrights, patents, and other such protections will eventually be impossible to enforce. And you know what? The world will be a better place for it.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I encourage any reader to comment when I say something that you think is particularly ingenious, idiotic, or bizarre. However I do reserve the right to remove comments that are offensive or do not pertain to the discussion at hand.</description>
      <enclosure url="http://brianhazzard.com/Brian_Hazzards_Blog/Blog/Entries/2012/2/11_The_Post_that_Started_it_All_files/SAM_1670.jpg" length="117702" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
